This is Nightmare Frequencies.
Tonight's transmission concerns an invasive species.
Found in every live stream, every comment section.
Every corner of the internet.
The troll who encounter one, do not feed it.
waking up tonight crawling from the darkness of a thousand screens living in the places somewhere
in between there's the first common goblin beating on a drum typing first knows what's going on the
grammar raises punctuation dead summoning forgotten commerce from the comments you read the impossible
They don't want discussion
They will side the feed
Eat of hate
Feed
Where's the tinfoil?
Sees while laughing
I down the moon
Guess a rack
Goblin dances in the fire
Changing subject
Just to fuel another rock
Internet's inside the feed
Digital phantoms
Features of the screen
I am machinist
Invisible skies
The watch is a thousand
Glowing eyes
Feeding every
that refuses to die
the sock puppet legion marches wearing stolen faces
moving through forgotten forums
occupying empty spaces
the clickbait reaper swings his golden scythe
heartbreaking the attention race
and thing a beast
the echo chamber demon
rollside the field
they screw to the darkness but dark
creatures of the screen
nightmare the unseen
is keeping strange alive, is replying.
Up the streets to giant states,
started as a hedge about four feet tall,
and swallows off.
Branches tangled thick as rope,
but he can see the garden home.
Walked in confidently,
fight, knit, and shout.
Formations living in a pool,
charges rent, and see flats without a light.
Don't go searching, that's energetic.
And I'm, where are you guys doing tonight?
I'm not very good. My show is not very good when I'm on my my my baby. It's almost I think it's almost it's almost done
So I hope you guys are good. I'd be like the beat is Bush song
You know, I like summer I hope you know, I think the summer is winning against
Beat is Bush and summer has some good pair of a good weed wacker. I think but
Yeah, I mean not like summer is a big fan of me. I went I mean I went to like
You know, I guess money for 20s chat today and I guess someone was there and I was like, then she said, oh, what do you call it?
What do you call having sex with a dead body? And she said nigger man's here or something like that
And I was like summer said the n word and then she's like, you know what's like yours is that you're a drunk and you're stupid
That's like I was kind of I was just kidding
I wasn't trying to like, you know
Get her in trouble or something like that. I just thought it was funny
but um
Yeah, but I may still enjoy her
You know winning that argument. I don't know like be this been like, you know beat in salmon
They're like the little team. Oh, it's like I can't even say if I say anything is chat
Oh go away. Everyone hates you site, you know, I think he doesn't seem to hate me. He plays my clips
Plays clips of me with her. I mean, it's like I just don't know how to talk in his chat. I guess
For Harley say anything and I just leave. I mean, it's like and then it's like, you know
I'm getting accused of like him butt-dialing her and sending Mason over there. Well, I did send Mason over there
But I thought Mason would be like a nice surprise
They a little ambassador for my show
She's a she like kicked him off right away, or I don't know. He wasn't there for very long
She got to hurry them through and then they played the clip and that's like and then of course my microphone
He came in here. I'm under a blanket plus like, you know
My microphone's like five feet away, and they're all full full full volume microphones all the way up
They're right at them
So it's like I can't even hear what I'm saying. You can just hear be
I'm like the teacher from like the peanuts and they're all like, you know
Like sports casters. I mean, it's like maybe I should get closer to my mic
But they can make you know, they can't fix the clip to make fix the audio a little bit
But no they want to make it sound like you know
I'm just like something significant little voice and like they got all these oh look she's cooking him. Oh, I'm so cooked
Whatever
This is a berry red bull very good. I don't know. I stopped by just to say hi
Um, you know, I guess the rumble streams are working again for panel verse. Maybe I'll get I'll do I'll do some rumble
See a trip kick is on her somebody. I don't know like because uh
Yeah, that making the beat is Bush song took a lot of energy out of me
So, um, let me see, you know, I like these classics. She's like, why are you playing old me?
I mean, it's like, I'm not like playing old you. I'm playing old episodes of my show or your show
That's on like, you know, trip kicks that I'm allowed to play because you've deleted it something, right?
Like why are you so afraid of your own children?
It's called, it's called, like, you know, best of.
I call it, I call it best of, the best of my show.
I bet as everyone's seeing Tommy and Jane
is making a fool of himself, this is a good one.
Let me see.
Where's Tommy and Jane is making a fool of himself?
This one, you know, it's pretty good.
Has its own.
Keep at it, keep it.
We keep on you, we're people.
That Persian spell put on me.
And it goes on and on and it goes on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and on and
I just wanted to come say hi to you, man,
and I hope you have a good day.
If you're around, I'll see you around here.
I'm looking for my brother over here.
He's small, autistic.
He gets lost.
He's kind of hard to find sometimes,
but his name's Sigmund.
If you see a little kid, brown hair,
he's got real big man boobies.
You can't miss him.
If he looks lost, maybe just say,
hey, your brother's looking for you.
Stay here, Tommy.
Mind if I get a hug to smell you a little bit closer. Okay, didn't mean to weird you out
My cousin touched my wiener
I wouldn't mind staying in your cheese
Sorry about that. Yeah, I haven't been taking mine
That she's actually knows me and he is spot-on. He knows when I'm not on my meds. You know that ooh
You got tuna here too, huh Bob? Oh wow. Whenever you have a minute, I think I kind of know.
Oh, you know, I'm gonna be honest with you real quick. It smells like my ex-girlfriend over here,
not in a good way. But that's what we love about seafood, right? You know, of course, of course,
but I just want to make sure that we're going, getting the best meat for the best price.
And then every time I keep thinking about the meat,
no freaky, I smell that smell and I'm wondering,
is that the product or is that you?
You know what, sir?
Maybe I see you have the tuna.
At least it isn't pooped tuna.
I'm gonna let you go about your work
and figure out what I want.
Apparently I'm not ready.
So just let me know.
Yes, sir.
I'll be back on the way out.
Let's get these two.
What you got there are some little taters little taters. No, not at all. I'm just looking around still
I was watching a movie. Yeah, I can see you filming and we had customers saying they kept saying profanity to them. Oh, no. No profanity
Okay, that's fine. I suppose I suppose I can respect that I didn't take my meds. So maybe
Yeah, I'll just walk out it's not a big deal. It's not like I'm having a psychotic episode or anything
I'm not gonna do anything. I'm not gonna do anything weird
I'm just gonna leave
Someone said that dive was she pulled out the kid they pulled out the Karen phones on the oh
Are you sure?
I'm leaving right now. I'm not gonna try to come back in or anything
I didn't do anything wrong.
See, then the other one came out.
The other Karen came out.
Look, they're going to come back on me.
I'm not doing anything wrong.
I'm pulling out the Karen Brigade on me, dude.
I didn't even fucking do anything wrong.
Yeah, she's like searching me down
and like trying to flag down security or something.
This is nuts.
I mean, I'm not gonna run. I hate Disney. All right, so let me sit down here
Is it okay if I take my shoes off and kind of oh, okay, cool. So you probably before I don't take them off
Sorry, I have a little autism in the way that I sleep is really weird. I usually start with something like this on my back
So I'm gonna just lay back
How much would how much was this again?
If it does that hardness feeling kind of go away,
it feels a little hard.
I take it the more you sleep in it and break it in,
all beds kind of have that.
I'm not familiar with memory so much.
This is how it would feel,
because I can't help but think like, ah!
Yep, I'm fine, I'm fine.
This is normal.
I actually do that about every night before I fall asleep.
And I have crazy night terrors.
But honestly even just putting me like sitting like this is putting me in a really dark place
No, I'm getting up right now. Let's see. It's gonna take us. Okay. I'm hurrying
Oh my god, that was total work. Oh me. Oh, that's you big guy
What did I do? Are you calling the police on me? I'll just leave
Are you calling the police on me?
What after you know him as the irregular guy should I be scared?
Can you tell me what he looks like so I don't get attacked out there?
Sorry, that scared the hell out of me because I see everybody looking outside and I'm wondering what's going on
That's pretty sorry you guys deal with that a lot. Is he dangerous?
Just have a annoying more than anything. Yeah, they were definitely trying to call the police on me. I'm not fucking stupid
I'm not fucking stupid
I'm getting the fuck out of here
Jesus Christ, I didn't even get to the other store yet you guys and they're already pulling this shit on a nickel
Right chat be ready for an interaction with the police apparently they're gonna find me
I'm right here
So they're gonna find me they're gonna fucking give me hell. I might get detained
Didn't he didn't
Let's see what else there
It's just ball asleep to this
Let's see. There's played doing some things
See who there's a guy looks like camel chicken and he looks a camel in that picture. Okay?
Arthur versus Christine featuring salmon and beat it. Let's watch this one. Hey, our lovers you need to see this
This gadget right here. Say meal
No, did he he's a big woman a gift code when you need to put your dick in
Arta opens his mouth
Oh my god
Fykes Lover
Arta the Big Sucker
Why the hate? Why the hate man?
Good evening. Good evening to all. How's everyone doing?
Say man, how you doing there brother?
How am I a dick sucker now?
Don't talk to me Nick
Someone said, Bravo.
Felipe said, hi, salmon.
Yo, so, Bita, I peeped the whole concrete shit.
I find that disgusting, and not only disgusting,
but I can't believe people really spend money to do that.
I mean, whatever, you know, that just comes with the, you know,
obsession of some people.
Well, are you drinking tonight?
No
Why would you ask that look look I'm drinking
How come you're stirring so much on Sykes earlier, I
Wouldn't say stirring. I was the interview. There was a
Mellwich like which is they stir the pod they're like ha ha ha at night. They're brewing. He's like a male version of a witch
It was an interview. I'd say it was an interview
Who gives a shit? Who do you think you are fucking uh who does who does like
You ever sing that song? I need you to sing that song. Hey, Karen. How have you been?
What song? I need you. This is you right here, Bita. This is what you do. Bita, I need you.
No, Bita, this is what you do to these, uh, you turn people gay and then this what happens to them.
Oh my god my internet. Oh we good. So you're gay now same man? I ain't gay. You just said she turns people gay.
I ain't gay. I don't even know what someone is talking about right now. You just said you turn people gay.
That's the rumor. That's the reputation that you turn men gay.
I'm worried they about to turn. I am worried. I mean shit. Oh my god
Kg brings all the gay boys to the yard same and I have a question if I could please me
Rumor has it that you and Christine will be meeting up. It is known that she is married
Uh, yesterday, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on,
Don't understand these people they talk they converse online and then what do you want to ask? Well, you do one doing that
Like nigga, you talked about it online my guy. Yeah, Arthur. You can visit me too. How about that?
Make sure you bring the empanadas. Thank you. All right, so
Chicken rumor again. Let me know when I can fucking ask the question fuck
Let me know when I can ask the question ask the question bitch
All right rumor hasn't you you'll be meeting up
Arthur, fuck you and your questions.
Go ahead, Christine.
Fuck you and your questions.
Married or not married, I can still do what the fuck I want.
And I am going to fucking New York,
not to fuck Sandman or any other man.
That is one thing I want to do.
So take your fucking questions elsewhere, bitch.
I love it. Yeah, why do you care? What do you see if she's not like, you know
He'll do the how to feel to be clapping today. Oh
How to feel to 517 tomorrow night, how'd it feel? Tell me how to feel bitch
You know what I do is none of your fucking business
What what I do is none of your fucking business nor should you be asking anybody?
About my life
Got it
Arthur are you there Arthur you're listening? Oh, he's listening. He don't want to answer because I won't
I'm letting her finish.
Well, there's nothing to, I will not be finished
as long as you're on here.
I walked out of my meeting to do this, okay?
Because you're a bitch and it's none of your business
and I'm tired of you starting shit.
Can I please ask the question and then you'll-
No, you cannot.
If it is anything to do with me,
if it is anything to do with me or me going to New York
with four of my friends, it's none of your fucking business.
Please just please it's a funny question. Please. No, it's not a funny question because I'm tired of you putting
My name in your fucking mouth all the time
Hey money, I'm not getting any please can I just finish the question? No, you can't
None of your business. Why isn't your business? I'm going to New York because I've talked about it
Please just let me ask a question
Why why does it matter to you? I go to New York
Why does it matter to you?
Man a location where we're gonna be if he wants to meet us why
Tell me why the thing that is you see how people treat me when I just ask questions. I'm not
She just wants to know why it's your business and then maybe it's it's like a question that's not related to
And you're you preface that I'm going to New York to meet Sandman. It's not accurate
I can understand Christine's anger, but let Arthur respond, please, Christine.
No, he has been doing this all day, everywhere.
That's why he got his ass clapped on psychs.
It is legit just a question, my goodness.
And yes, I clapped your ass, okay?
Okay, I get it.
Christine, please.
And I'll do it again and again and again.
I'm begging you, please.
No.
I'm not doxing anyone.
I'm not threatening you.
It's not a matter of doxing.
It's a matter of you putting your note in my fucking bag.
What are you?
I really don't get what the fuck's so bad about asking
You caring about me going to New York, I mean yeah
People do have a point you did make it public right you didn't have I did but his thing is he
Made it perfectly clear on several channels that
Christine's coming to New York to meet Sandman
Not that I'm coming with a group of women not that there's going to be many different people that were meeting men and women
Arthur wants some action, that's it.
I think where it went wrong when Arthur said a married woman because as a woman,
a married woman, she should be able to go. This is not a third row.
Just because I'm married doesn't mean I'm married.
Exactly. Oh my gosh, she's going to ask me not.
Your bill went up the moment they installed the new meter. Here's what it's detecting
and how to fix it. When they replaced your old meter,
I've taken a cruise without my husband.
Did I say that you're going to cheat on your husband?
I never said that.
I always said it.
I don't know.
I'm going to marry him.
You're going to have to do what you have to do.
I'm going to tell him.
Are you guys going to do what you like?
I'm going to do anything.
I'm going to marry him.
I'm going to tell him.
have to do with anything.
Arthur, are you reacting to that right away with like,
are you insinuating that she's gonna cheat on her husband?
Like, you're also worried about me being married or not.
Why?
Christine, how many friends you bring in though?
There's four of us.
There's me and four others.
They sing it too?
They sing it over me.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, hey, Christine, three or three or make three or marry your single one.
You can't afford the one that you can't afford.
Is she single table game?
Yeah.
You got any photos? I'm kidding. I'm kidding. Oh my god. Yeah, new sims are coming out of the bushes
Christine it's Christine. I might have I might have company
I'm just kidding. I'm kidding. I might have I might have company in the career. I might have a little party for y'all
You heard so you have a fish
You know, I might have some baby since the cat again
Rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
Hey, you want to go to New York with us to sweetheart? I'll let you there's
there's me and for the women going. We are going to have a blast KK that'll be great
Hey, I have no problem K could come to New York with me.
Oh my goodness. Money and two. Hey Arthur, money's meeting two. You want to ask him the same fucking question?
Go ahead, go ahead, Arthur, go ahead.
Oh my God, you're going to meet up with Christine in the future as we all know she's married, correct?
Okay?
I don't know.
What the fuck are we living in like the... I don't know, 1800s now?
Where fucking people cannot believe that.
You just go back to the cave or something.
I'm asking like a lot of fucking cave on the afterthought.
I have children his age.
Okay, can I finish the question and then you can rebuttal?
Get it! Get it! Get it shorty! Get it shorty! Get it!
Once every quarter, we have an evening meeting.
Okay, okay. Once every quarter, we have an evening meeting.
It's almost done. They're just doing it.
Okay, okay. I'm going to go and meet them.
It's only six years.
No!
Arthur, if you were to come to Toronto,
I wouldn't meet you for a drink, anybody.
Anyone of you guys out in town.
I mean, one of you guys in the back of the mall.
I agree.
And you're married, so why are you pressing anybody else? We're meeting with somebody else.
Who is pressing who? Let me finish the question, then you can rebuttal. Fuck.
Wow, are you triggered?
Yeah, because you're a stupid bitch.
And go your spot. Okay. Alright. I'm the stupid bitch, but you've been fucking sitting here and you're still triggered that you're going to call me a stupid bitch. Call me a stupid bitch, you're going to kick you.
That is true. You got a point there.
the fucking question all right Sam and rumor has it you're gonna have people
coming over be the what's up you know my goodness
it can't be this difficult to ask dude coming over that's a summer I think
summer's coming please do it please we got like three single ladies coming in
this one I can't afford are we gonna be busy
You guys got some ADHD, all right, Sam and in the near future rumor has it that you're
going to be meeting Christine.
Christine is married, right?
Okay, Sam and will you be wearing your shiesty your mask when you meet her or are you going
to, you know, reveal your face show your face or your teen is not a doctor so she might
get the face.
She might get the face called you're
Okay, see that was my question
Planning to meet up with a pdD mask or anything
He was just gonna go as a human being and just frickin like chill and people can be friends. They could be different
But be the keepin be the keep in the comment, please which comment there's a bunch of
Kks little fella do some IRL with your company and make some content
Let me finish as opposed to be big hook
Big heavy, do some IRL with your company and make some content.
She called, she named it heavy by the way, not me.
She called it the heavy.
Yo, okay, okay, okay, make some content with your man Black.
Black is cracker, let's get to that.
Let's get to that, let's get to that.
Let's get to that.
What's up, man?
Am I witnessing a street fight or something here?
What's going on?
Nah, dude.
Like, if anyone's gonna fuck with Sandman, it could only be me.
Not this bitch.
Fuck this fucking...
Oh!
Oh, this bitch.
Oh, but then you then you said that blackest crackers name is banned from the chat
It is it is I try to type it in in the chat many times and it's banned. Oh
My god
Yep, yep, I try typing it in in the live chat
I can never get it through and I then I just typed in lol then that goes through but you can't put his name in
Maybe that's why maybe she wants to summit trip maybe she won a summit trip Arthur
No, it's not that I'm banned. That's not true. That's not true. That's probably why your butt hurt again every time.
No, listen to me. Listen to me. Listen to me. When I type in LOL, it goes through. But when I type in Blackish Cracker, it does not go through.
Word that you don't want to mention on your list
Nah, maybe they broke up. Maybe they make a fucking
No, you can literally put her like
Hold on Arthur. Hold on. He didn't hear it the way he's opposing
He ain't got the heavy
Not the heavy after shit that moved further
The nigga don't got the heavy
I know Mermaid, but you're here for it. Okay. All right, I kiss the lady.
Louis Armstrong. Oh, not the Louis Armstrong. Your hair.
Oh, my God. Well, that's pretty.
Of course.
Well, I'll be up on back later.
Where'd it go? You're blinding your night, right? Oh, you are? I'm sorry.
Hi, that was Chippin' Cake. Yeah, classic episode. I'm sorry, guys.
But I hope you have a good night and maybe I'll be back.
Okay, love you.
Thank you so much.
Muah!